{
  "SpotTheAns": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": " _______ refers to the process of locating and removing the errors in a program.",
      "options": ["Analyzing", "Correcting", "Debugging", "Executing"],
      "answer": "Debugging"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "A pointer is ________________",
      "options": [
        "The address of a variable",
        "An indication of the variable to be accessed next",
        "A variable for storing addresses",
        "The data type of an address variable"
      ],
      "answer": "A variable for storing addresses"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "The name of a function ends with _______",
      "options": ["Double quotes", "Single quotes", "Parenthesis", "#"],
      "answer": "Parenthesis"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "The feature that allows the same operations to be carried out differently depending on the object is ________",
      "options": ["Polymorphism", "Polygamy", "Inheritane", "Multitasking"],
      "answer": "Polymorphism"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "If you declare two objects as Customer firstCust, secondCust; which of the following must be true?",
      "options": [
        "Each object will store a separate copy of any static member data",
        "Each object will store a separate copy of any member functions",
        "Each object will store a separate copy of any nonstatic data members",
        "You cannot declare two objects of the same class"
      ],
      "answer": "Each object will store a separate copy of any nonstatic data members"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Inheritance is the principle that _______",
      "options": [
        "Classes with the same name must be derived from one another",
        "Knowledge of a general category can be applied to more specific objects",
        "C++ functions may be used only if they have logical predecessors",
        "One function name may invoke different methods"
      ],
      "answer": "Knowledge of a general category can be applied to more specific objects"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "User-defined functions can be _______",
      "options": [
        "Value-returning functions only",
        "Void functions only",
        "Either value-returning or void functions",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": "Either value-returning or void functions"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "A function that is called automatically each time an object is created is a(n)",
      "options": ["Constructor", "Contractor", "Builder", "Architect"],
      "answer": "Constructor"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "If you assign a default value to any variable in a function prototype's parameter list, then _______",
      "options": [
        "All other parameters in the function prototype must have default values",
        "All parameters to the right of that variable must have default values",
        "All parameters to the left of that variable must have default values",
        "No other parameters in that prototype can have default values"
      ],
      "answer": "All parameters to the right of that variable must have default values"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "A function that is called automatically each time an object is destroyed is a _______",
      "options": ["Constructor", "Destructor", "Destroyer", "Terminator"],
      "answer": "Destructor"
    }
  ]
}
